https://iccidd.org/privacy-policy/

Your privacy is important to us. It is ICCIDD’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, https://iccidd.org/, and other sites we own and operate.We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.Your continued use of our website will be regarded as an acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.This policy is effective as of 1 January 2019.Please make sure to also carefully read through our Terms Of Service.Featured Posts Wrecked Pre Workout Review: The Best Pre-Workout Of 2020?May 4, 2020Wrecked Pre Workout Review: The Best Pre-Workout Of 2020? Semenax Reviews: Read Before Buying This #1 Male EnhancementMarch 13, 2020Semenax Reviews: Read Before Buying This #1 Male Enhancement D-Bal Review: Insane Results From This Legal Steroid?March 9, 2020D-Bal Review: Insane Results From This Legal Steroid? Trenorol Review: Worth The Crazy Amount? #1 Legal SteroidMarch 6, 2020Trenorol Review: Worth The Crazy Amount? #1 Legal Steroid Annihilate Review: #1 Insane New Plant Anabolic Supplement?February 27, 2020Annihilate Review: #1 Insane New Plant Anabolic Supplement?Popular Posts The 3 Best Stim Free Pre Workouts Revealed December 19, 2019 Wrecked Pre Workout Review: The Best Pre-Workout Of 2020? May 4, 2020 The 5 Best Male Enhancement Pills To Boost Sexual Performance November 8, 2019 SARMs For Sale: Our 3 Best SARMs Vendors Revealed! November 14, 2019 Crazy Bulk Reviews: #1 Mind-Blowing Results Inside November 20, 2019CategoriesSUPPLEMENTS 21BODYBUILDING 14MALE ENHANCEMENT 5SARMS 2WORKOUT 1Newsletter Get Discounts & Early Access on SALES
Subscribe to our mailing list to get the new updates! Enter your Email address
Back to top button
Close FacebookTwitterYouTubeInstagram
Search for:
Popular Posts BODYBUILDINGThe 5 Best Legal Steroids For Gaining Muscle Revealed! November 1, 2019 Wrecked Pre Workout Review: The Best Pre-Workout Of 2020? May 4, 2020 The 3 Best Stim Free Pre Workouts Revealed December 19, 2019 The 5 Best Male Enhancement Pills To Boost Sexual Performance November 8, 2019 Testofuel Reviews: My 3 Month Experience & Mind-Blowing Results December 18, 2019Most Commented
December 19, 2019The 3 Best Stim Free Pre Workouts Revealed
May 4, 2020Wrecked Pre Workout Review: The Best Pre-Workout Of 2020?
November 8, 2019The 5 Best Male Enhancement Pills To Boost Sexual Performance
November 14, 2019SARMs For Sale: Our 3 Best SARMs Vendors Revealed!
November 20, 2019Crazy Bulk Reviews: #1 Mind-Blowing Results Inside
December 5, 2019Transparent Labs Preseries Bulk Reviews: Read Before Buying! Recent Comments
Samira Wow, great article. Going to try out the Transparent Labs...
Close
Search for
Close Log In
Forget?
